[{"answer": "Well, you know, the angels in the story of the first Christmas said three things.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "What is the purpose of Christmas?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Oh, of course.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "And do you get people from all religions?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, we're an overtly Christian church.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "-- or a Jew or whoever it may be?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, I think there are three different factors.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "But why do you think it's on the decline?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I don't say that I like it, but I try to use it.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Do you like the extraordinary position of responsibility you now have -- now have for yourself?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, no, it's not healthy.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "-- is it healthy?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "ARREN: Well, the studies show, no, it doesn't.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "And they then devote a large chunk of that to helping needy people, people less fortunate than themselves, does that balance it out?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Have you had big problems in that marriage, if you like?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Do people give up on marriage too early these days?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, and -- and the problem is, you're an imperfect person and you're going to marry an imperfect person.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "They don't fight enough for it?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, probably in my teenage years, I fell in love every week.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Rick, how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Oh, it's not only natural, it's euphoric.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "-- it feels completely natural?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Great question.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "What -- why can you not allow them to have that euphoria that you had, with all the rights that go with that kind of relationship?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Can I pull that back?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "-- supporting and voting and making legal gay marriage?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Well...", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "-- it is just wrong?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I don't see that happening, because I have a world view based on scripture that remains unchanged.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Or could you see a time when you may say, you know something, America has changed, I'm prepared to change?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "No, no, nobody -- you can love anybody you want to in our freedom...", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "What does being free mean?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "But what is freedom?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "You...", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Is that if -- if a mean -- a word means a certain thing, and it's not -- and it's not my word and all of a sudden I say, well, I'm that, is that fair?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "I'm -- I'm not sure what you're saying.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "So you wouldn't have amended anything to the Constitution?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "I think the Bible is true; not everything in the Bible that is explained in the Bible does the Bible commend.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "You think everything in the Bible is completely accurate?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "How do you try and change the fact that Christmas becomes this crystallization for many people of all that's terrible in their lives?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "It is a tradition we call Birthday Party for Jesus.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "He is.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "He's an impressive guy, isn't he?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "Well, it's funny how this thing started, Piers.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "How do you combine diet with prayer?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "The number one thing -- you know, of course, diets are diets and health plans are health plans.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 802, "question": "So what are the key things you have to do with this diet?", "qSentId": 801}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 834, "question": "You drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 833}, {"answer": "Never have.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 837, "question": "Never had (INAUDIBLE) nip, not even at Christmas?", "qSentId": 836}, {"answer": "Well, the message of Christmas is that that babe in the manger didn't stay a babe in the manger.", "docId": "121224pmt", "aSentId": 849, "question": "What would you say?", "qSentId": 848}]